# Nozomi Sugezawa

Web Developer

#### CONTACT

Kingston, ON, Canada (437)230-8833

nzm020129@gmail.com

GitHub

Linkedin

Portfolio

#### **SKILLS**

Front-End:

- · HTML, CSS, JS
- Responsive Design
- Bootstrap library
- jQuery
- React
- Angular

#### Back-End:

- NodeJS
- JSON
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- AWS
- Firestore
- Heroku

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Innovative Solutions: Actively contribute valuable ideas in agile meetings to support the business development of upcoming features.

**Multilingual Proficiency:** Fluent in English, Japanese, and French, offering a global perspective and effective communication in multicultural environments.

#### **EDUCATION**

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development, CareerFoundry, May 2023 - July 2024

Diploma in Bilingual Language Skills English And Japanese, CanPacific College, March 2019 - May 2019

Bachelor of Arts in French literature and language, Kwansei-Gakuin University, April 2008 - March 2012

## **SUMMARY**

Customer-centered Web Developer, with over 10 years of experience in the Hospitality industry. Blending a deep commitment to exceptional service with robust technical skills, and creating user friendly applications. Ensuring an outstanding user experience in every project with active listening and problem-solving abilities.

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

## myFlix

Personal Project, CareerFoundry 09/2023 - 12/2023

- Created a RESTful API using Node.js and Express, that interacts with a nonrelational database (MongoDB).
- Developed single-page, responsive application, developed with React and React-Redux.
- · Implemented user registration, movie search, and favorite list functionalities.

See GitHub Repo

#### MEET

#### Personal Project, CareerFoundry 02/2024 - 03/2024

- Designed a progressive web application with React to display events from Google Calendar, achieving cross-platform functionality and offline availability.
- Led a test-driven-development approach, achieving 95% test coverage with unit and integration tests (Jest), acceptance tests (Cucumber), and end-to-end testing (Puppeteer).
- Utilized serverless functions (AWS Lambda) for user authentication and authorization (OAuth), improving security and scalability.

See GitHub Repo

#### RECENT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **SALES ASSOCIATE**

Valextra | Osaka, Japan 09/2022 TO 02/2023

- Anticipated every situation to understand customers' potential needs and made customized proposals.
- Delivered knowledgeable, friendly support in high pressure situations, enhancing customer satisfaction and loyalty.
- Streamlined daily operations in a self-directed work environment, improving efficiency and productivity.

#### **WAITRESS**

Take-sushi | Kingston, ON 12/2019 TO 10/2021

- Consistently maintained high customer satisfaction scores by multitasking effectively and prioritizing tasks.
- Enhanced guest experience by providing personalized service, including food upsells and recommendations, resolving complaints promptly.
- Upheld restaurant hygiene standards by maintaining clean and organized dining areas, contributing to a positive dining environment.